rugsusa.com 2019-02-24

# Rugs USA Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY

Rugs USA is committed to respecting the privacy rights of our customers and all visitors to our web site. We take this matter very seriously, and have instituted many policies and procedures to insure that none of your privacy rights as stated herein are ever violated. The following outlines Rugs USA 's privacy policy and details the measures we have taken to safeguard and protect your privacy, while providing you with a unique and rewarding online shopping experience. By visiting Rugs USA , you are agreeing to the policies detailed below.

#### What if i communicate with Rugs USA electronically?

When you send an email to Rugs USA or visit the web site, you are communicating with us electronically. When you send an email to Rugs USA , you consent to receive communications from us electronically in response. Please note that this does not constitute opting in to our email or direct mail lists. Rugs USA may communicate with you by email, by updating or posting notices on the web site. You agree that all agreements, notices, disclosure and other communications that Rugs USA provides to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communication be in writing. All communications with Rugs USA become the property of Rugs USA.

#### What information does Rugs USA collect?

In order to serve you better, Rugs USA collects and stores your personal information when you: (i) create an account (ii) sign up to be notified of special deals like discounts and exclusive offers; or (iii) enter a contest or promotion on our site. An account is created when you do one of following things: make a purchase on Rugs USA , create a wish list on Rugs USA , or register for an account on Rugs USA , or enter certain Rugs USA sweepstakes. When creating an account, we ask you for your first and last name, your e-mail address, a password, and perhaps some other similar information. If you are making a purchase, we will additionally ask you for your billing address, shipping address, and credit card information.

Our system also may gather information about the areas you visit on our site as well as the IP address you use to connect to our site. We may use this data internally only for 2 reasons: 1) to personalize your experience on Rugs USA .com and the marketing materials you receive from Rugs USA or its partners and 2) to prevent fraud on your account. We would not share any of this data on an individual basis (we may share it in an aggregate form without personal identifiers) with any outside company other than perhaps consultants or service providers of Rugs USA who were assisting Rugs USA in serving you better. We do not keep track of where you go on the World Wide Web. We also utilize Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Using the [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads), you can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads.

#### What does Rugs USA do with this personal information?

Your information is used to process your orders and personalize your shopping experience on Rugs USA , for internal purposes and to comply with any legal requirements. By storing your personal information on a secure server, Rugs USA is able to shorten your checkout process and allow you to check your order status online.

At Rugs USA , we also review what kinds of products appeal most to our customers as a group. This statistical information helps us improve our offering in the same way that other companies change their catalog based on what sells best. We may also use information about the kinds of products you buy from Rugs USA to make other marketing offers to you. Of course, you always have the option to opt-out from receiving such offers (for instructions on how to opt-out, please see below).

#### Does Rugs USA share any information it collects with outside parties?

We may use your purchase information about the products you buy from Rugs USA to make other marketing offers to you. Of course, you always have the option to opt-out from receiving such offers (for instructions on how to opt-out, please see below). We may share this information with consultants or service providers to help Rugs USA serve you better. Of course, to the extent that we would ever share any of that information with a consultant or service provider, we would only do so if that party agreed to protect your private information by adopting a privacy policy at least as stringent as our own.

Rugs USA may collect your email address via cookies and pixels on the Website through the use of trusted third party partners. These partners may combine your email information with other information they have access to such as mailing address so that Rugs USA may serve relevant marketing offers to you via direct mail. If you do not want Rugs USA to collect information about you, please see below for instructions on how to opt-out.

#### How does Rugs USA safeguard my personal information?

Rugs USA has implemented a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information supplied by you is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and securely stored in Rugs USA 's database.

#### Does Rugs USA provide a way to update or remove personal information?

Rugs USA provides a my account feature on our website which allows you to modify and/or remove most of your personal information. This page can be accessed by clicking the my account link at the top of every page on the site. Rest assured that all of your information within my account is secure and accessible only by you or limited Rugs USA personnel.

#### How does Rugs USA use my e-mail address?

Your e-mail address is used to create and identify your account on Rugs USA . Your e-mail address is also used by Rugs USA to correspond with you about any orders that you may place or to notify you with the results of any contests you may have entered. We may also use your e-mail address to notify you about important functionality changes to the Web site, new Rugs USA services and special offers and promotions we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, or would like to opt-out of receiving e-mail of this kind, simply click on the "Unsubscribe" link that appears at the bottom of any email and follow the simple instructions to have your email address removed from the list of customers who receive notices of new functionality, services, special offers and promotions. We offer a convenient unsubscribe option on our site as well, click here to unsubscribe.

#### Does Rugs USA use "cookies"?

A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web site that is saved on your hard disk by your computer's browser. The cookie holds information a site may need to personalize your experience and to gather web site statistical data, such as which pages are visited, the internet provider's domain name and country that our visitors come and the addresses of the sites visited immediately before coming to and immediately after leaving Rugs USA.com. However, none of this information is associated with you as an individual. It is measured anonymously and only in the aggregate. The information in the cookies lets us trace your "click stream" activity (i.e., the paths taken by visitors to our site as they move from page to page). Cookies do not capture your individual email address or any private information about you.

Rugs USA may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our web site as well as third party companies to provide tracking and analysis of information and data collected from visitors to our web site. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous and Rugs USA reserves the right to provide that information and data to these third parties.

#### Google Privacy Policy

Certain features of our site utilize the Google Maps API and its use is subject to the [Google Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

#### Your consent

You acknowledge that this privacy policy is part of the terms of service and you agree that using this site signifies your assent to Rugs USA 's privacy policy. Rugs USA reserves the right to change the terms of service, including this privacy policy, at any time, without advanced notice. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

If you have any questions please contact [info@rugsusa.com](mailto:info@rugsusa.com). You can also call us at 1-609-447-4515 or by postal mail at the following:

Rugs USA  
8 Santa Fe Way  
Cranbury, NJ 08512
